freetwitterdesigner.com 2016-12-06

# Free Twitter Designer

## PRIVACY POLICY

Zugara, Inc. ("Zugara," "we" or "us") is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining your confidence and trust. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect information from you through the Website, why we collect this information, how we will use or disclose this information and how you may update or delete identifiable information about you from our records. By using the Website, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to comply with and be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the Website.

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or delete portions of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Your continued use of the Website after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to regularly check the Website to determine if the Privacy Policy has changed, as indicated by the "Date Last Revised" line at the bottom of this page.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies, organizations or websites that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Zugara Terms of Use . All capitalized terms in this Privacy Policy have the meanings given to them in the Terms of Use, unless otherwise defined herein.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

####  Personal Information You Provide to Us: 

We do not request users of the Website to provide any information that may be used to personally identify an individual, such as your name, a physical address, an email address or other contact information ("Personal Information"). If you submit any Personal Information to the Website, we will not use or share it with any other person except as provided in this Privacy Policy. If you send email or other communications to us, we may retain and store those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve the Website or our services. 

In order to allow users to take advantage of certain features on the Website, we sometimes request users to sign in to their Twitter accounts. For example, you may choose to allow the Website to directly update the background image on your Twitter profile with the image created on the Website. In that case, you will be provided with a link to the Twitter.com website where you can sign in to your Twitter account and authorize the Website to update your Twitter profile. We will neither receive nor store any Personal Information you submit to the Twitter.com website or any other third party website.

####  Personal Information Collected Automatically: 

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Website. Generally, our service automatically collects information on our server logs from your web browser regarding your usage of the Website. Examples of information we may collect automatically from all users include the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; and full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) click stream data, including date and time, and content you viewed on the Website. We only use this data in aggregate, anonymous form (that is, as a statistical measure), and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate, anonymous data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of the Website so that we can make the Website appealing to as many users as possible. 

### USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We will not use or transfer Personal Information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses. We neither rent, sell, nor otherwise provide your Personal Information to anyone, except as described below: 

Protection of Zugara and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Zugara, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Our disclosures may occur under circumstances where we may not be authorized to advise you of such action. 

Business Transfers: If Zugara or its assets are acquired by a third party, or in the unlikely event that Zugara goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred to a third party. By accessing the Website or downloading or using any content we offer on the Website, you acknowledge that these transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Zugara may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of Personal Information, we cannot guarantee you that the information we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

### CHOICES FOR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You can always opt not to disclose information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain features of the Website or to otherwise use the Website. You may also request deletion of your Personal Information by contacting us by email, phone or fax as set forth below. 

### A SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT CHILDREN

If you are under 18, you should use the Website and our services only with involvement of a parent or guardian. Children under 13 may not submit any Personal Information to us, and if we discover that we have inadvertently gathered any such information from a child under 13, we will take appropriate steps to delete it. We comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (which is available at <http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm>) and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13.

### LINKS

The Website may contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours. 

The links from the Website that go to other websites are for convenience only, and do not imply that we endorse or approve of those websites. We have no control over the content found on other websites and make no warranties or representations as to the accuracy or adequacy of any information found at such websites. We are not responsible for any loss, injury, claim, liability, or damage related to your use of the Website, whether from errors or omissions in the content of the Website or any other linked sites, from the Website being down or from any other use of the Website. Your use of the Website and others’ websites is at your own risk. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites that are linked to us. 

### INFORMATION SECURITY

We make every effort to safeguard your Personal Information. We commit to use security procedures to protect Personal Information you submit to us from misuse or unauthorized disclosure. However, like other websites, we cannot guarantee that it is completely secure from people who might attempt to evade security measures or intercept transmissions over the Internet. 

### CONTACTING US

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at the Website, please send a detailed message to [feedback@freetwitterdesigner.com](mailto:feedback@freetwitterdesigner.com), call us at 310-945-4950, or send a fax to us at 310-945-4951. If at any time you believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy or you have a complaint regarding the way your Personal Information is being handled, please contact us by email, phone or fax (as indicated above). We will resolve disputes under this Privacy Policy and, if necessary, correct any problem. 

Date Last Revised: July 7, 2009
